### **CONTACT**

pathianitajoyce@gmail.com

7331130822

• Hyderabad, India

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/ani-joyce-b6a9ab191/

### **SKILLS**

**ATS Application Tracking System** 

**Head Hunting** 

**Contract Negotiation** 

HRM Knowledge and Expertise

Lateral Hiring IT & Non IT

#### **AWARDS**

WOW Award Goldman Sachs

Super Squad Award Goldman Sachs

Hired to Hire Award Hamstech India Pvt Ltd

Extra Miler Award Goldman Sachs

Passionate GOLD Award Hamstech India Pvt Ltd

Super Employee - NO Leave Award GE Money Servicing

## Anitha Joyce

#### TALENT ACQUSITION PROFESSIONAL

#### **SUMMARY**

Talent Acquisition professional with good experience in hiring and retaining positions at all levels of an organization. Develop and executive recruitment strategies to network and hire most qualified candidates by measuring and optimizing recruiting programs.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Deputy Manager AMS (Goldman Sachs - Client)

Dec 2021 - Present

- Managing the entire recruitment process Identifying resources reviewing qualification, interviewing the candidates, finalizing the selections in discussion with HM
- Involved in different Business Units with Engineering hiring and given 60 offers successfully in past one year and 74 selects with a pipeline of 986 candidates across all levels of hiring
- Handled sourcing for clients from Junior, mid-level and leadership hiring for various units across Goldman for Technology Hiring
- Interviewed candidates with leadership team to determine behavioral and cultural fits
- Worked with department heads to understand their talent needs, and reduced the time to hire to fill those positions by 37%
- Investigated gaps of interviews funnel, and discussed compensation packages of prospective hires
- Reduced average time to hire by 15days with consistent communication across professional channels, s, including LinkedIn and internal database Created candidate pipeline for Nishe skills for future hiring purposes across all levels
- Reviewed 3000+ resumes to determine candidates credentialss Assisted Hiring managers in schuleding interviews, screening profiles
- Handles 12recruiters and 5 interns to conduct market research and review skills

# Talent Acquisition Specialist Hamstech India Limited

Mar 2019 - Sep 2021

- Managed full recruitment cycle to keep company fully staffed across 8Locations in Hyderabad and various PAN India locations with 4 different verticals
- Headed campus recruitment efforts with 4 job fairs at the university, sourcing interns
- Collaborated with leadership on recruitment strategies, development plans, perforance management and employee engagement to improve retention rates by 12%
- Provided guidance on employee relations and matters of corrective action that reduced turnover rates by 8%

- Managed company organizational structure, responisibilities and staffing levels
- Caoched managed s & employees on perforamance metrics Completed HRIS data entry, reporting, auditing & processed payroll requests
- Handling recruitments smoothly across all levels and sharing best practices to improve the quality of recruitment with the team members
- Mentored team of 6 recruiters and sourcers, allocation of work, SLA's and handled PMS metrics within the team.

#### Human Resource Officer Sitel India Pvt Ltd

Sep 2013 - Mar 2014

- Plan and conduct new employment orientation & induction to foster a positive attitude towards the growth of the organizational objectives
- Facilitated onboarding sessions and on the job training for new hires bolstering employee job position knowledge and skill set
- Grievance handling session to understand challenges and provide resolution.
- Single-handed handled R&R employee engagement & Employee satisfaction event arrangements.
- BGC& Reference checks Getting the background and reference check done as per the client Hosted company wide town hall meetings (All hands)to convey updates
- Talent Acquisition support given in campus/walk-ins/vendor management bulk hiring for non-engineering internal business units

## Process Developer - HR GE Money Servicing Ltd - Synchrony

Mar 2007 - Sep 2012

- Managed and administered 100% of pre-employment assessments to prospective candidates.
- Assisted with new employee onboarding and ensured all prememployment forms were completed with 72hours
- Researched and adapted a new benefits plans that helped to improve employee satisfaction by 9%
- Collected feedback after final round of interviews and put together comprehensive compensations packages for new hires
- Created and posted job ads, scheduled interviews, and managed prememployemnt drug screenings and background checks
- Assisted with benefits administration inducing COBRA reporting leave administration and employee hike and benefits.

### **EDUCATION**

Master of Arts - Economics
Osmania University (Campus Student)

Bachelor of Arts - Economics Kasturba Gandhi College - Osmania University